In this video, I'll be showing you how to configure the Windows Hello for business.
Well, don't forget, we have the Windows Hello and the Windows Hello for business.
So this is utterly going to be focused on Windows Hello for business.
We have to configure it, what you need to do, you need to go to devices, and here we have
an enrollment.
And in enrollment, you can see we have the Windows Hello for business.
But first of all, what is utterly the Windows Hello for business?
Well, if you are using your Windows client operating system, you don't want to work for a company,
you have your own personal device.
There's what we call the Windows Hello.
So I call it Microsoft Windows Hello is an authentication technology that allows users
to sign in to their Windows devices using barmetric data or pin instead of a traditional password.
So it provides an enhanced security, which gives it kind of a more resistant to two-factor
authentication and a built-in, brute force protection.
Well, the Windows Hello for business is an extension of the Windows Hello which you use on a regular device.
But this utterly provides an enterprise-grade security and management capabilities,
which include device attestation, certificate base authentication, and also conditional access policy.
So I just want to show you how to utterly configure it using Microsoft Intune.
Well, you still need to utterly deploy it to your devices and make sure that your users are totally
forced using policies to utterly forced to use the Windows Hello for business and any device
that or any user that does not use the Windows Hello for business, that device may be marked as non-compliance.
So what you need to do is to go to Windows Hello for business and here you can see at this moment it is not configured.
So here you can say you can say "configure Windows Hello for business", then we're going to say enabled.
And now you can say we have the different options.
So well, you want to say it's usually trusted platform model.
I'm not that you can also say require, but I'm going to put this as preferred.
And for the minimum length for pin, you can see we have 6, but the minimum is hydraulic,
you can see it's between 4 and 1 around 27.
So here you can see the maximum I can just put 20.
And lower case letters, you can see we have different options.
We can say well, I want to allow it.
And upper case as well, I want to allow which means they will be forced to use the lower case
and upper case, because what disabled these, which for example they can just use just numbers.
And again we have the pin as far as shown this, because here you can see it's never
but you can't really enter a day and say well, I want to put it for 90 days,
that the user will be forced to actually change their pin.
And then we have remember pin history, I can't really put like 5 so that the users should not
use the same pin all the time.
And you can see it's allowed by matricle dedication, of course you want to configure it to yes,
and then you use enhanced anti-spuffin.
Well, I'm going to leave this to not not configured.
Allow full signing, we can't just, can't say no, well, we can't say yes.
And here you can see we have the enabled enhanced signing security.
And I can just say well, let me use the enhanced signing security
to be enabled on system with capable, capable hardware.
Well, remember not all had all devices have this feature.
So I'm just going to leave that for not configured and use security keys for signing,
also I'm going to leave that for not configured.
And then I will click save.
Here you can see it's been, it's been saved.
But next in a different video, I'm going to be showing you how to actually implement it
to your devices, to your company, and make sure that every single user, your company is
being forced to, or users, are being forced to actually use Windows Hello for business.
And if they don't use it, those devices that are not configured with Hello for business
will be marked as known compliance.